University of Connecticut, Center for Oral History Interviews Collection 1984.0025
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Gravetending in the New Mansfield Cemetery, 1997-1998 (Box 24)
  - Morrissette, Constance (26 pp.), 1998 February 25; 1984-0025/GravetendingNewMansfieldCemetery/Morrissette (Box 24, Folder 6 [39153013992856])
  - Wittig, Faith (20 pp.), 1998 February 6; 1984-0025/GravetendingNewMansfieldCemetery/Wittig (Box 24, Folder 7 [39153013992864])
- The Greater Hartford Process (Coventry Experience), 1972-1975 (Box 27, Box 28, Box 25, Box 26)
  - Charles Andreuk (11 pp.)
  - Bryant Andrews (8 pp.)
  - Ann Baker (32 pp.)
  - Roger and Lois Barrett (9 pp.)
  - Jesse Brainard (32 pp.)
  - Debbie Breault (34 pp.)
  - Richard Breault (9 pp.)
  - Richard Brooks (30 pp.)
  - Clement Bouchard (6 pp.)
  - Roberta Bynes (32 pp.)
  - Al Carilli (36 pp.)
  - Joyce Carilli (22 pp.)
  - Arnold Carlson (17 pp.)
  - Donald Conlon (25 pp.)
  - Frank Connolly (31 pp.)
  - Harold Crane (14 pp.)
  - Richard Cromie (40 pp.)
  - James Curry (35 pp.)
  - Maureen Danehy (7 pp.)
  - Laurier F. Demars (26 pp.)
  - Virginia Diehl (91 pp.)
  - Fred and Priscilla Doyle (24 pp.)
  - John Druge (38 pp.)
  - Malcolm Edmonds (23 pp.)
  - Bob Farrar (31 pp.)
  - Max Ferguson (44 pp.)
  - Mr. and Mrs. William Fisher (18 pp.)
  - Robert Fitch (18 pp.)
  - John Fitzgerald (19 pp.)
  - Rose Fowler (10 pp.)
  - Ruth French (10 pp.)
  - Frances Funk (25 pp.)
  - Holly Gantner (35 pp.)
  - Betty Gardner (12 pp.)
  - Lorraine Glynn (45 pp.)
  - Alvin R. Goodin (24 pp.)
  - Paul Goodin (13 pp.)
  - Judy Halvorson (21 pp.)
  - Peter Halvorson (33 pp.)
  - Dave Hannon (37 pp.)
  - Margaret Hemphill and Les Barber (17 pp.)
  - Wilfred and Ruth Hill (20 pp.)
  - Thomas Holzer (24 pp.)
  - Patricia Hughes (21 pp.)
  - Jon Jennings (29 pp.)
  - Robert Keller (32 pp.)
  - Donald Kingsley (30 pp.)
  - Joseph Kornfeld (29 pp.)
  - Roslyn Kornfeld (24 pp.)
  - John LaBelle (13 pp.)
  - Michael Lepter (10 pp.)
  - Wesley Lewis (45 pp.)
  - Peter Libassi (59 pp.)
  - Arthur Lumsden (17 pp.)
  - Dan Manley (25 pp.)
  - David and Donna McKinney (23 pp.)
  - William Miller (58 pp.)
  - Harvey Moger (17 pp.)
  - Dennis Moore (38 pp.)
  - Jim Moore (23 pp.)
  - Marion Morra (37 pp.)
  - Richard North (32 pp.)
  - Charles Nyack (45 pp., 40 pp.)
  - Joe Pacheco (52 pp.)
  - Antonio Peracchio (8 pp.)
  - Daryl Perch (21 pp.)
  - Al Phillips (19 pp.)
  - Frank and Mary Risy (10 pp.)
  - Allen Sandberg (14 pp.)
  - Harry Siebert (33 pp.)
  - Don and Ruth Smith (43 pp.)
  - Don Smyth (45 pp.)
  - Sondra Stave (56 pp.)
  - Dave Tolzmann (16 pp.)
  - Dave Tomm (32 pp.)
  - Judy Wallace (33 pp.)
  - Craig Wallace (13 pp.)
  - Brian Walsh (50 pp.)
  - Robert Walsh "Skip" (24 pp.)
  - Doug Webster (21 pp.)
  - Ernie Wheeler (15 pp.)
  - Chuck White (41 pp.)
  - Bernard Wilbur (20 pp.)
  - Robert Young (44 pp.)
- Holocaust Survivors In The Connecticut Region, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Box 30)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Dana L. Kline. Interviews By: Dana L. Kline. Undertaken in conjunction with the Center for Judaic Studies and Contemporary Jewish Life. See also: Holocaust Programs (1992, 1993), listed under Conferences, Lectures, Etc. and Peoples of Connecticut-Jewish.]
  - Kurt Appel (transcript incomplete)
  - Dr. Joe Berger (34 pp.)
  - Jacob Biber (41 pp.)
  - Mania Blank (53 pp.)
  - Rabbi Hans Bodenheimer (51 pp.)
  - Dr. Rita Botwinick (40 pp.)
  - Henry Drobiarz (31 pp.)
  - Leopold Gerechter (63 pp.)
  - Dr. Louis Gerson (182 pp.)
  - Isidore Greengrass (109 pp.)
  - Paul Greenspan (46 pp.)
  - Liese Himmel (28 pp.)
  - Martha Klein (92 pp.)
  - Vladka Meed (21 pp.)
  - Dr. Elizabeth Rablen (24 pp.)
  - Dr. Haddassah Rosensaft (26 pp.)
  - Julius Rytman (45 pp.)
  - David Schwitzer and Zelig Schwitzer (45 pp.)
  - Fred Seeman (20 pp.)
  - Joseph Shepard (31 pp.)
  - Carol Vinick (29 pp.)
  - Mindy Weisel (39 pp.)
  - Sylvia Zeldis (35 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_c3aad7bcc71d2889a5dea42584d2075c)
- Individual Oral Histories, 1967-1989 (Box 32, Box 31, Box 35, Box 36, Box 33, Box 34)
  - unspecified
    [Interviews By: Various.]
  - Gov. Raymond Baldwin (1969-1970, 2320 pp., indexed)
  - Maurice Bicknell (1972, 25 pp.)
  - Merlin Bishop (1971, 99 pp., indexed)
  - James MacGregor Burns (1977, 37 pp.)
  - Wilbur Cohen (1975, 48 pp.)
  - Frank Connor (1969, 95pp. indexed; Also transcript to his "Talk to Apprentices, 1967)
  - John Driscoll (1969-1970, 82 pp.)
  - Finis Engleman (1973-1974, 152 pp.)
  - Clair Elston (1970, 52 pp., indexed)
  - Franklin Farrel III and Frank Joy (1986, 100 pp.)
  - Robert Giaimo (1981-1984, 105 pp.)
  - Theodore Gold (1967, 11 pp.)
  - Dorothy Goodwin (1986-1992, 437 pp.)
  - Gov. Ella Grasso (1979, 12 pp.)
  - Erwin Griswold (1989, 258 pp.)
  - Elsie Hill (1968, 169 pp.)
  - Leonard B. Hough (1970, 33 pp., indexed)
  - Rhoda Jenkins (great-granddaughter of Elizabeth Cady Stanton, 1982, 44 pp.)
  - Dan W. Lufkin (talk at Connecticut Pre-Session Legislators Conference, 1972, 14 pp.)
  - Doris McBee (Housed in the peoples of CT, 1976, 29 pp.)
  - Joseph Nerden (1975, 166 pp.)
  - Marion Pardus (Housed in Peoples of CT, 1977, 27 pp.)
  - Abe Ribicoff (Channel 3 WFSB Public Affairs Presentation, 1977, 60 pp.)
  - Joseph Rourke (1970, 85 pp.)
  - William J. Sanders (undated, 84 pp.)
  - Sigrid Schultz (1977, 40 pp.)
  - Joseph Soifer (1979, 9 pp.)
  - Gov. Wilbert Snow (1969, 166 pp.)
  - Malcolm Wilson (1981, 33 pp.)
  - Chase Going Woodhouse (1977-1979, 313 pp., indexed)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_c1a94bd0965fad785de2b52f8bbe04f5)
- Italian Immigrant Gardens, 1985-1987 (Box 37)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Theresa Deshefy-Longhi. Interviews By: Theresa Deshefy-Longhi. Each interview consists of a six page informative questionnaire, accompanied by a drawing of the resident's landscape.]
  - Mary and Olga Anastasio
  - Helen Carrano
  - Morris Cavalieri
  - The Cirillo Family
  - The Favretti Family
  - Mrs. (Merlone) Flagge
  - Mildred Insogna and Mary Tafuto
  - Mrs. Herman Kuiken
  - Joseph Palumbo
  - Antonio Parisi
  - Michael Perrotti
  - Pasquale Poletti
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_b3f52cc24d4d0e64e9612528954291d9)
- Last Drift: Connecticut's Last Commercial Windship Sailors, 1987 (Box 38)
  - Bell, Jr., Wallace Henry (45 pp.) (Box 38, Folder 1 [39153030467148])
  - Bloom, Hillard (45 pp.) (Box 38, Folder 2 [39153030467155])
  - Ciaurro, William (73 pp.) (Box 38, Folder 3 [39153030467163])
  - Dowd, Charles Albert (53 pp.) (Box 38, Folder 4 [39153030467171])
  - Palmer, Samuel Pierson (53 pp.) (Box 38, Folder 5 [39153030467189])
  - Pramer, Joseph Aloysius (43 pp.) (Box 38, Folder 6 [39153030467197])
  - Ventulette, Sr., Robert Louis (46 pp.) (Box 38, Folder 7 [39153030466041])
  - Wagner, John Charles (40 pp.) (Box 38, Folder 8 [39153030466058])
- Living And Learning 1908-1983, 39 Woodland Street Hartford, 1982-1983
  - unspecified
    [Interviews By: Sharon Fowler. All interviews indexed. A joint project of the Center for Oral History, the Center for Insurance Education & Research, and the MBA Program, Hartford.]
  - Lawrence J. Ackerman (26 pp.)
  - James E. Brennan (24 pp.)
  - William T. Fisher (41 pp.)
  - Melancthon W. Jacobus "Chick" (23 pp.)
  - Ralph. H. Lundberg (18 pp.)
  - Zenon S. Malinowski (34 pp.)
  - Mary Kay Schnare and Robert Butler (51 pp.)
  - Andrew H. Souerwine (35 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_e6daee44ed907b0a8400b72c96042d18)
- The Making Of Urban History, 1974-1992 (Box 40)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Bruce M. Stave. Published in "The Making of Urban History Series," Journal of Urban History except where noted (*). See Also: Interviews listed under Foreign Interviews and Chinese Urbanization and Urban Planning & American Studies in China.]
  - Alan Artibise* (1978, 33 pp.)
  - Francois Bedarida (1980, 29pp.)
  - Thomas Bender (1987, pp.)
  - Brian J. L. Berry (1976, 48pp.)
  - Asa Briggs* (1976, 34 pp.)
  - Ellsworth Brown (1990, 35pp.)
  - Mr. and Mrs. S.G. Checkland* (1976, 38 pp.)
  - G. Davison (1977, 24 pp.)
  - A.J. Dyos (1976, 37 pp.)
  - Michael Frisch (1989, 103 pp.)
  - Ingrid Hammarstrom (1982, 32 pp.)
  - Kenneth Jackson (1991, 76 pp.)
  - Frank Jewell (1990, 26 pp.)
  - David Kahn (1992, 46 pp.)
  - Zhou Lei (1985, 49 pp.)
  - Gilbert Stelter (1978, 40 pp.)
  - Anthony Sutcliff (1976, 63 pp.)
  - Sam Bass Warner, Jr. (1983-1984, 43 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_f909ff2785900090bf9bc3149a931559)
- Manchester-Cheney Oral History Project, 1971-1991 (Box 42, Box 41, Box 44, Box 43)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: John F. Sutherland, Director, Institute for Local History. Interviews By: Various. Produced under the auspices of the Manchester Community College Institute of Local History, copies of these oral histories are available for personal/educational use only. Permission to publish must be obtained from the Institute. See also Cheney Brothers Silk Manufacturing Company Records.]
  - John Adams (48 pp.) [20th century Labor relations at Cheney Mills]
  - Nathan G. Agostinelli (35 pp.) [Political career]
  - Isabella Anderson and Nancy Horner (54 pp.) [Life and labor in Manchester in 20th century]
  - Edson M. Bailey (18, 29 pp.) [Manchester during the Depression and WWII]
  - Herbert Bengston (31 pp.) [Swedish-American life in Manchester, Cheney Mills]
  - William E. Buckley[ (29 pp.) [Growing up in Manchester Green, 1900-1913]
  - Elizabeth Chase (51 pp.) [Clifford Cheney family]
  - Violet Cheesman (28 pp.) [Life and labor in Manchester and the Cheney Mills]
  - Douglas T. Cheney (24 pp.) [Growing up in Manchester in 1920s/30s, family life, Mills]
  - John P. Cheney, Jr. (22 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - John W. Churila (16 pp.) [Lithuanian-American life in Manchester]
  - Thomas Cordner (13 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Ann J. Curry (36 pp.) [Manchester in the post-WWII era]
  - Mary C. Dannaher (42 pp.) [Political and civic activities in Manchester]
  - Mary DellaFera (72 pp.) [Changes in patterns of social services in Manchester]
  - Harriet B. Dzicek (41 pp.) [Immigration from Poland to Rockville, briefly at Cheney Mills]
  - Leonard Eccellente (38 pp.) [Italian-American life in Manchester]
  - Gladys Fallon (32 pp.) [Life and labor on Manchester]
  - Filomena Farr (22 pp.) [Italian-American life in Manchester]
  - Vivian Ferguson (53 pp.) [Manchester during Depression and WWII]
  - Michael D. Foglio (41 pp.) [Growing up in Manchester and working at Cheney Mills]
  - Louise Gaggianesi (47 pp.) [Immigration from Italy and life in 20th century Manchester]
  - Howard Gilman (39 pp.) [Tobacco growing, South Manchester RR, growth of Manchester]
  - Guido Giorgetti (22 pp.) [Immigration from Italy, Cheney Mills]
  - Anthony Golas[Cheney Mills] (27 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Wanda and Hayden Griswold (27 pp.) [Manchester during the Depression]
  - Lillian J. Gustafson (58 pp.) [Life in Manchester and the Cheney Mills in 20th century]
  - Joseph Handley (28pp.)
  - Mary McFarland Handley (35 pp.)
  - Ludwig Hansen (21 pp.) [German-American life in Manchester, Cheney Mills]
  - Albert Harrison (67 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Irma Harrison (27 pp.) [Swedish-American life in Manchester]
  - Mrs. Harold Heffron (17 pp.) [Life and labor in the Cheney Mills]
  - Charles S. House (36, 42 pp.) [Career, Manchester 1918-1930s]
  - A. W. Illing (34 pp.) [Teacher and administrator]
  - Jessie M. Johnson (34 pp.) [Life and labor in Manchester and Cheney Mills]
  - John A. Johnston (39, 19pp.) [Manchester 1918-1930s]
  - Everett Kennedy (42 pp.) [Manchester]
  - John Kluck (20 pp.) [Immigration from Germany, Cheney Mills]
  - Alice Koski (19 pp.) [Life and labor in Manchester]
  - Horace Learned (37 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Joseph Leary (24 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - James T. McLaughlin (52pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Alice Muirhead (40 pp.) [Childhood on Manchester's West Side during 1930s]
  - Anna C. Murphy (54 pp.) [Life and labor in Manchester and Cheney Mills]
  - Emily Cheney Neville (14pp.) [Growing up in a Cheney household]
  - Thomas O'Neill (pp.) [Immigration from Ireland and life in Manchester]
  - Margaret Olmstead (13 pp.) [Life in Manchester 1920-1940]
  - Ida Ostrinsky (22 pp.) [Immigration from Russia and life in 20th century CT]
  - Ignazio Ottone (34 pp.) [Immigration from Italy, life and labor in Manchester]
  - Mr. and Mrs. Luigi Pola (28 pp.) [Immigration from Italy]
  - James Reardon (40 pp.) [Chief of Police in Manchester]
  - Lucy Richardson (37 pp.) [Immigration from Ireland]
  - Albert J. Robinson (18 pp.) [Pine Street, Fire House activities]
  - Frank C. Robinson (41 pp.) [Cheney Street Fire Station]
  - John Robinson (63 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Joseph Sartor (56 pp.) [Growing up in Manchester and working at Cheney Mills]
  - Margaret Schleminger (33 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Catherine Shea (56 pp.) [Teacher in Manchester]
  - Alice St. Louis (30 pp.) [Cheney Mills in the 1930s]
  - Frank Stamler (28 pp.) [Life in Manchester during WWII]
  - Ann Struzenski (46 pp.) [Domestic servant in several Cheney households]
  - Elsie Sweeney (33pp.) [Cheney family and Mills]
  - Mrs. Frances Tedford (38 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Leon Thorp (43 pp.) [Life in Manchester]
  - James Tierney (35 pp.) [Growing up in Manchester during the Great Depression]
  - Fred E. Thrall (24 pp.) [Cheney Mills]
  - Frank Waddell (40 pp.) [Growing up in Manchester]
  - R. Bruce Watkins (13 pp.) [Watkins Family of Manchester]
  - Esther H. Weiss (25 pp.) [Growing up and Teaching school in Bolton and Manchester]
  - Hannah Cheney Williams (34 pp.) [Cheney family]
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_25d2a4d60afaed0f6f23c44f06454b54)
- Millworkers of Willimantic, 1979-1980 (Box 45)
  - unspecified
    [A student project coordinated by Daniel Schwartz. Interviews By: Various. A photographic exhibit, "Thread City: Its Workers and Their Mills", was held in conjunction with this project. Locations included: Jillson House, Willimantic, CT; Booth Dimock Library, Coventry, CT; University of Connecticut Library; and Connecticut State Library, Hartford, 1980-1981. Please Note: Several of these interviews are included in Thomas Beardsley's Willimantic Industry and Community: The Rise and Decline of a Connecticut Textile City. (Windham Textile and History Museum, Willimantic, CT, 1993). The project is also on file at the Windham Textile and History Museum, Willimantic, CT.]
  - Richard Benoit (18 pp.)
  - Romeo and Mary Benoit (14 pp.)
  - Vera Bobrek (18 pp.)
  - Celeste Roy Bucko (19 pp.)
  - Miss Celia (13 pp.)
  - Henry Costello (20 pp.)
  - Leona DeLude (16 pp.)
  - Lil Despathy (12 pp.)
  - Mr. and Mrs. (Margaret) Dubina (40 pp.)
  - Rose Dunham (10 pp.)
  - Daniel Gallagher (21 pp.)
  - Charles Hill (24 pp.)
  - James Lee (34 pp.)
  - Isabelle Moran (29 pp.)
  - Gail Smith (14 pp.)
  - Alice Stabile (11 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_0c81284451ed1e8ed12e8469268d2193)
- Nisei at UConn, 2003 (Box 46)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Bruce Stave. Interviews by Bruce Stave and Sandra Astor Stave. This project was conducted as part of a reunion and symposium held 16-19 October 2003 for Japanese-American students who attend the University during World War II and was sponsored by the Institute for Asian American Studies and the Asian American Cultural Center.]
  - Aisawa, Shiro (47 pp.), 1984-0025/Nisei/Aisawa
  - George M. Fukui (42 pp.)
  - Toshie Hawasaki Kato (34 pp.)
  - Kay Kiyokawa (29pp.)
  - Jim Nakano (39 pp.)
  - Satoshi Oishi (32 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_2439fdeb2184dffd3008d36fb384b50f)
- Peoples of Connecticut, 1973-1976
  Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews by: Holly Izard, Matthew Magda, Lenore Cavallero, Rosemary Nardi, and others. This oral history project was part of a larger project directed by William V. D'Antonio and funded by the United States Department of Education. It also includes an archival collection, the development of curriculum guides and demographic mapping. Please consult the Guide to the Peoples of Connecticut Project Records and the digitized portions of the collection. See also: Bruce M. Stave and John Sutherland, with Aldo Salerno. From the Old Country: An Oral History of European Migration to America. (Twayne Oral History Series, 1994.)
  - African-American Interviews
    - Alexander, Mary (47 pp.), 1975 February 24; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/AfricanAmerican/Box47/Alexander (Box 47, Folder Alexander: [39153019935701])
    - Felton, Gladys (10 pp.), 1975 May 5; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/AfricanAmerican/Box47/Felton (Box 47, Folder Felton: [39153019935719])
    - McCoy, Laura Belle (23 pp.), 1975 March 23; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/AfricanAmerican/Box47/McCoy (Box 47, Folder McCoy: [39153019935727])
    - Napper, Bernice Norwood (27 pp.), 1975 February 20; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/AfricanAmerican/Box47/Napper (Box 47, Folder Napper: [39153019935735])
    - Norcom, Rebecca (26 pp.), 1975 April 29; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/AfricanAmerican/Box47/Norcom (Box 47, Folder Norcom: [39153019935743])
    - Weston, Bertram (36 pp.), 1975 May 5; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/AfricanAmerican/Box47/Weston (Box 47, Folder Weston: [39153019935750])
  - French-Canadian Interviews
    - Babineau, (Mrs.) Roger (9 pp.), 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/French Canadian/Babineau (Box 48, Folder Babineau: [39153013992609])
    - Bolduc, Emmanuel (10 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/French Canadian/Bolduc (Box 48, Folder Bolduc: [39153013992914])
    - Depot, Cyril (Mr. and Mrs.) (36 pp.), 1975 April 7; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/French Canadian/Depot (Box 48, Folder Depot: [39153013992617])
    - Ethier, Daniel (12 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/French Canadian/Ethier (Box 48, Folder Ethier: [39153013992625])
    - Laramee, Adrien (11 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/French Canadian/Laramee (Box 48, Folder Laramee: [39153013992633])
    - Morin, Daniel (11 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/French Canadian/Morin (Box 48, Folder Morin: [39153013992641])
    - Phaneuf, Alda (22 pp.), 1975 April 9; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/French Canadian/Phaneuf (Box 48, Folder Phaneuf: [39153013992658])
    - Therrieult, Giselle (29pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/French Canadian/Therrieult (Box 48, Folder Therriault: [39153013992666])
  - Irish Interviews
    - Archambault, Christine (11 pp.), 1975 November 13; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Archambault (Box 49, Folder Archambault: [39153013992674])
    - Begley, John (36 pp.), 1975 April 9; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Begley (Box 49, Folder Begley: [39153013992682])
    - Boyle, Thomas (26 pp.), 1975 April 15; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Boyle (Box 49, Folder Boyle: [39153013992690])
    - Carey, Kathryn (29 pp.), 1975 April 22; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Carey (Box 49, Folder Carey: [39153013992708])
    - Coppinger, Thomas G. (25 pp.), 1975 February 17; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Coppinger (Box 49, Folder Coppinger: [39153013992716])
    - Curry, Paul (50 pp.), 1975 January 29; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Curry (Box 49, Folder Curry: [39153013992724])
    - Dalton, Anne (20 pp.), 1975 April 22; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Dalton (Box 49, Folder Dalton: [39153013992732])
    - Dillon, Thomas (21 pp.), 1975 June 30; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Dillon (Box 49, Folder Dillon: [39153013992740])
    - Droney, James (14 pp.), 1975 January 15; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Droney (Box 49, Folder Droney: [39153013992757])
    - Ducey, Charles (14 pp.), 1974 October 18; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Ducey (Box 49, Folder Ducey: [39153013992443])
    - Evelyn, Sister Mary (36 pp.), 1974 December 13; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Evelyn (Box 49, Folder Evelyn: [39153013992450])
    - Forde, Gerald F. (42 pp.), 1975 June 5; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Forde (Box 49, Folder Forde: [39153013992468])
    - Harkins, James (36 pp.), 1975 April 14; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Harkins (Box 49, Folder Harkins: [39153013992476])
    - Healy, Mary (22 pp.), 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Healy
    - Heaphy, Joseph (43 pp.), 1975 May 6; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Heaphy (Box 49, Folder Heaphy: [39153013992500])
    - Keeley, George B. (36 pp.), 1975 November 18; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Keeley (Box 49, Folder Keeley: [39153013992492])
    - Kennedy, Russell (21 pp.), 1975 June 17; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Kennedy (Box 49, Folder Kennedy: [39153013992518])
    - Kenney, Helen and Helen Conlin (19 pp.), 1975 April 3; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Kenney_Conlin (Box 49, Folder Kenney: [39153013992526])
    - Kernan, John Una (Mrs.) (40 pp.), 1975 February 9; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Kernan (Box 49, Folder Kernan: [39153013992534])
    - Keyes, Thomas (10 pp.), 1974 November 1; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/Keyes (Box 49, Folder Keyes: [39153013992542])
    - O'Brien, Thomas (29 pp.), 1975 April 21; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/O'Brien (Box 50, Folder O'Brien: [39153013992559])
    - O'Carroll, Father Patrick J. (36 pp.), 1974 December 12; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/O'Carroll (Box 50, Folder O'Carroll: [39153013992567])
    - O'Connor, William (37 pp.), 1975 June 4; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/O'Connor (Box 50, Folder O'Connor: [39153013992575])
    - O'Donovan, John and Kathleen (28 pp.), 1975 January 9; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/O'Donovan (Box 50, Folder O'Donovan: [39153013992583])
    - O'Rilley, Edward (48 pp.), 1975 May 21; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Irish/O'Rilley (Box 50, Folder O'Rilley: [39153013992591])
    - Reardon, Msgr. Edward (25 pp.), 1975 January 13 (Box 50, Folder Reardon: [39153013993086])
  - Italian Interviews
    - Avallone, Anthony S. (23 pp.), 1975 April 22; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Avallone (Box 51, Folder Avallone: [39153013993094])
    - Avella, Matteo (19 pp.), 1975 January 23; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Avella (Box 51, Folder Avella: [39153013993102])
    - Balsamo, (Mr.) (31 pp.), 1975 January 28; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Balsamo (Box 51, Folder Balsamo: [39153013993110])
    - Bologna, Sando (20 pp.), 1975 January 11; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Bologna (Box 51, Folder Bologna: [39153013993128])
    - Buccino, Antonio (21 pp.), 1974 December 13; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Buccino (Box 51, Folder Buccino: [39153013993136])
    - Candelori, Ottairio (Mrs.) (31 pp.), 1974 December 17; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Candelori (Box 51, Folder Candelori: [39153013993144])
    - Cannata, Joseph (21 pp.), 1975 January 26; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Cannata (Box 51, Folder Cannata: [39153013993151])
    - Capobianco, Gennaro J. (33 pp.), 1974 October 15; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Capobianco (Box 51, Folder Capobianco: [39153013993169])
    - Caterino, Elia (18 pp.), 1975 April 29; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Caterino (Box 51, Folder Caterino: [39153013993177])
    - Cretella, Albert (14 pp.), 1974 November 7; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Cretella (Box 51, Folder Cretella: [39153013993193])
    - D'Antonio, (Mr. and Mrs.) (99 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/D'Antonio (Box 51, Folder D'Antonio: [39153013993227])
    - DeLauro, Louise (23 pp.), 1974 November 7; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/DeLauro (Box 51, Folder DeLauro: [39153013993235])
    - DiLella, Albert (Mrs.) (16 pp.), 1974 December 5; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/DiLella (Box 51, Folder DiLella Albert: [39153013993268])
    - DiLella, Paul (16 pp.), 1974 November 14; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/DiLella (Box 51, Folder DiLella Paul: [39153013993250])
    - DiScala, George, Sr. (39 pp.), 1975 May 5; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/DiScala (Box 51, Folder DiScala: [39153013993276])